<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2015bPM.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2015bPM.s.1">The meeting was a crucial decision-making time where we discussed design and function ideas, and thought about practical and trendy design concepts.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015bPM.s.2">I asked the three other contributors to present their information, and we made decisions based on everyone's findings, and the objectives we agreed upon.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015bPM.s.3">We are going to have a simple, international-friendly design that will be both practical, simple to use, and friendly.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2015bPM.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2015bPM.s.4">Tara will research whether or not SMART technology is feasable.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bPM.s.5">Genevieve will investigate trends.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bPM.s.6">Poppy will probably come up with some ideas of how it will work, what materials we'll need, etc.   -I'll write up the meeting minutes and try to bring all the presenter's ideas together in the next meeting.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2015bPM.pdecisions.1">
   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2015bPM.s.7">we'll only have television function buttons.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bPM.s.8">It will lighten up at the touch of a button (may cost more).</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2015bPM.s.9">the buttons will be in the shape of numbers with soft plastic for RSI suffers.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bPM.s.10">We'll try to target a more young audience with trendy interchangable--and inexpensively made--plates.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bPM.s.11">We'll have an adhesive alarm system.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2015bPM.pproblems.1">
   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2015bPM.s.12">our ideas might be expensive to create.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bPM.s.13">We have to make sure that the remote can be used internationally.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
