<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2009bPM.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2009bPM.s.1">We met and discussed the functional limitations and directions for the remote control.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009bPM.s.2">First, I presented some limitations imposed by the board on what needs to be included in the RC to help guide further work.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009bPM.s.3">Then the three other members of the team did brief presentations of their findings and recommendations for the project.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009bPM.s.4">From these recommendations and the general vision for the project, we dicussed and brainstormed to rule out ideas that we thought were inappropriate and kept ones that we felt were beneficial.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2009bPM.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2009bPM.s.5">Each member will be instructed precisely how to go about his or her work via email.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2009bPM.pdecisions.1">
   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2009bPM.s.6">The RC will be aimed at a younger demographic .</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2009bPM.s.7">It will be primarily designed for simple function in order to meet the needs of simplicity and style that young users appear to demand .</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009bPM.s.8">The logo and colours will be incorporated on a touchscreen and on the physical case.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2009bPM.s.9">Due to design limitations, plastic will be used for the case.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009bPM.s.10">Efforts will be made to obtain quality, presentable materials to construct the case.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009bPM.s.11">Costs will be taken into account for these design suggestions.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2009bPM.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2009bPM.s.12">It was noted that I did not delineate tasks clearly enough.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
