<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2013aME.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2013aME.s.1">This meeting familiarised the team members with each other and revealed some characteristics we each find desirable.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013aME.s.2">This information is useful to me as I will keep it in mind when we make group decisions, since I can appeal to the things each of us find enviable.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013aME.s.3">Following this gentle introduction, the team leader presented the project goals, discussed the number of remote controls to be sold at what price point, assigned tasks to each team member and planned the next meeting.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013aME.s.4">My main focus will be on finding out what consumers want beyond the group's annecdotal stories to descriptions of concrete, desirable, sellable remote control units.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013aME.s.5">I contributed a few ideas off the top of my head which weren't really elaborated upon too extensively by other group members.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013aME.s.6">I look forward to finding out more about their prespectives at the next meeting.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2013aME.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2013aME.s.7">Marketing Person: create user specification for next meeting.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013aME.s.8">Project Manager: remind us of our roles and seek deliverables at next meeting.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013aME.s.9">User Designer: determine the human user interaction needs of such a tool.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013aME.s.10">Industrial Designer: determine the functional constraints we need to work within.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2013aME.pdecisions.1">
  <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2013aME.s.11">-I need to create a user requirement specification.</sent>    <sent nite:id="ES2013aME.s.12">The industrial design has to reflect on hardware constraints.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013aME.s.13">Have another meeting.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2013aME.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2013aME.s.14">There were no problems or difficulties in the last meeting.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
