<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2013dME.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2013dME.s.1">This final meeting included a prototype presentation by the design team.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013dME.s.2">They showed two examples that fulfilled the design standards we devised at the last meeting and after a discussion we chose an attractive yellow block with oversize black scroll-esqe buttons.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013dME.s.3">While the underlying technology isn't cutting edge, the design itself is rather unusual, approachable and refreshing.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013dME.s.4">Following the design presentation where they delineated the substances and manufacturing techniques to be used, I briefly introduced an evaluation metric.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013dME.s.5">Then, using the white board, I incorporated the marketing concerns brought up in the earlier meeting and as a group we judged the prototype on how well it adhered to these issues.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013dME.s.6">Overall, the evaluation result was 1.88 with 1 being best and 7 being worst.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013dME.s.7">This was a fantastic success.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013dME.s.8">The last order of business was filling out the manufacturing spreadsheet to discover the production price per unit which, due to the design choices, came in =A32 under the =A312.50.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2013dME.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2013dME.s.9">The task is complete!</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2013dME.pdecisions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2013dME.s.10">We chose the chunkier, less fruity prototype.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2013dME.s.11">--</sent><sent nite:id="ES2013dME.s.12">We made judgements about the success of the prototype.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013dME.s.13">We filled out the manufacturing spreadsheet.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2013dME.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2013dME.s.14">There were no problems and this meeting moved along very swiftly and efficiently.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
