<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2014aME.pabstract.1">
     <sent nite:id="ES2014aME.s.1">We discussed the product - a new television remote control that is more trendy and user-friendly (market research tells us this is what people want).</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014aME.s.2">The market is international, and the project manager presented the information about costs, price and profit.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014aME.s.3">We discussed problems with current remote controls, and whether the remote should just control the television, or whether it could control other devices.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014aME.s.4">We decided it should be robust.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014aME.s.5">We did not discuss how to market the remote control - I suggested a functionality concept for the remote which involved it controlling other devices but we decided to stick to the brief of a TV remote.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014aME.s.6">I need to think of ways to market the device for the next meeting.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2014aME.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2014aME.s.7">The project manager will summarise the last meeting and devise an agenda for the next one.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014aME.s.8">The industrial manager will find out about what materials the remote can be made from, and how we're going to manufacture it.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014aME.s.9">The user interface manager will find out how we're going to utilise these materials to make the experience of using the remote pleasurable.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014aME.s.10">The marketing manager will be finding out how we're going to market this device and what product features people want the most.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2014aME.pdecisions.1">
    <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014aME.s.11">Decided to stick to a TV remote.</sent>    <sent nite:id="ES2014aME.s.12">Decided that it had to be robust.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014aME.s.13">Decided that there are too many buttons on current remotes.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2014aME.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2014aME.s.14">The project manager had a few computer problems, but this did not undermine his role as the facilitator.</sent>    <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014aME.s.15">We had trouble sticking to talking about those things associated with our roles - i.e. I was describing a design idea, the project manager was chipping in with suggestions, etc..</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
