<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2006aUI.pabstract.1">

   <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.1">The meating met its aim in that the people at the project had a chance to meet each other, and get to know each other to some extent.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.2">As for the product, I personally was hoping to leave the meeting with a clearer idea about what we wanted to achieve.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.3">Probably this is going to be in the agenda of one of the next meetings.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.4">However, we specified the following three goals about the project, namely that we want it to be original, trendy and user friendly.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.5">The meeting did not satisfactorily explain my responsibilities in the project, but this might also be fine, considering that we are in the very initial stage of the project.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2006aUI.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.6">Think about the responsibilities assigned to them, or that they think they are responsible for.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.7">Interface designer - what functions should the remote control have?</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.8">Industrial designer - maybe what we might need in the production process - e.g. materials, resources, machines.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.9">Prepare the agenda of the next meeting, and new goals to be set.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.10">Marketing manager - some market research.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2006aUI.pdecisions.1">
  <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.11">Product has to be original, user friendly and trendy .</sent>           <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.12">A note on originality - cannot compromise user friendlyness - in major points has to conform to standards set by previous remote controls.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.13">Three satges in product development: functional design, conceptual design, detailed design.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.14">Production cost not to exceed EUR 12.50.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.15">Selling price EUR 25.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2006aUI.pproblems.1">
  <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.16">No major difficulties occurred this time.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.17">Maybe the fact that our role specifications are still not entirely clear.</sent> <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2006aUI.s.18">.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
