<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2015cME.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.1">The third meeting started at 2:15.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.2">Poppy started things off with a presentation on components design.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.3">She outlined the functional parts of the circuit board: diodes, transistors, resonators, resistors, capacitors and LED, as well as the importance of an integrated circuit (the main chip).</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.4">Poppy spoke of varoius energy source options, including basic battery, kinetic energy, solar power, and hand-powered dynamo.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.5">We ruled out the last two.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.6">She went on to discuss the case, where our options are plastic, rubber, wood and titanium.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.7">Again we ruled out the last two and agreed on a combination of plastic and rubber.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.8">Moving on to buttons, Poppy explained the differences between simple, regular and advanced electronics for running the buttons- based on previous decisions, we will be using regular.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.9">Tara made her presentation next.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.10">She explained that user interface is the aspect of a system which is seen and/or perceived by the user, as well as the commands accessed by the user to control and in-put data.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.11">There are two types of interface, graphical and comman, however we will be dealing with comman as it is more relevant for a remote control, not to mention cheaper and simpler.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.12">She warned us about the tendency of remote control creators to design products that are too cluttered.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.13">We went on to discuss the details of the buttons, i.e. will they be a part of the rubber casing or on the solid remote control skeleton?, should the style/colour change?, how large and what kind of tactility?</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.14">I gave the marketing update last.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.15">I spoke about our priorities of  creating a remote that has a fancy look-and-feel, is technologically innovative and easy-to-use.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.16">I also reported that fruits and vegetables are the newest trend in Milan and Paris.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.17">Heather concluded the meeting by asking the designers to come up with a prototype.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.18">I will be writing a marketing product evaluation.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.19">Meeting was over at 2:50 pm.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2015cME.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.20">Designers are creating prototype.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.21">I will draft a marketing product evaluation.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.22">Product manager will calculate the costs.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2015cME.pdecisions.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.23">We will use kinetic power, which is one of the newest energy sources.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.24">It will involve the user shaking the remote to energize it.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.25">This fits in with our mandate to create a product that is technologically innovative.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.26">The main structure of the remote will be in hard plastic.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.27">The casing and buttons material will be rubber.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.28">This has several benefits, mainly:       -provides additional protective layer if remote is dropped.</sent>       <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.29">Easy to create unique designs on the rubber casing.</sent>       <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.30">Minimizes effects of RSI.   -buttons will be simple electronics, however the LED will mean the use of regular electronics.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.31">Command interface is simpler, cheaper and more effective, so we're going with that.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.32">We will avoid a clutter of buttons.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.33">Marketing will involve promoting the hassle-free, minimal buttons approach.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2015cME.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.34">Research into kinetic energy.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015cME.s.35">What designs will the face plates have?</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
