<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2015aME.pabstract.1">

   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.1">M.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.2">The kick-off meeting went well.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.3">There were four of us present- Heather, the Project Manager; Tara, the Interface Designer; Poppy, the Industrial Designer; and myself, Genevieve, the Marketing Expert.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.4">We began by introducing ourselves and outlining our roles in the product design.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.5">Heather went on to brief us on the purpose and agenda of the meeting.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.6">We learned that we are to go through the functional, conceptual and detailed design of a remote control.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.7">This remote is to be original, trendy and user-friendly.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.8">After this introduction, Heather asked each of us to draw a picture of our favourite animal, explaining our reasons.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.9">(Elk, Cat, Dog and Butterfly).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.10">After the animal fun we went on to discuss the finance issues of our product:   -sell for 25 euros.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.11">Profit aim of 50 million euros.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.12">Production cost of 12.50 euros.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.13">International marketing.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.14">The group did some remote control brainstorming:   -original design.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.15">Buttons should be user friendly and easy to use in the dark.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.16">Remotes are often lost- some sort of tracking device?</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.17">Should be universal considering our international market (but maintain uniqueness).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.18">After this, Heather outlined some of the research that needs to be done before our next meeting.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.19">I will be looking at user requirement specifications.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.20">The meeting concluded at 11:17am.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2015aME.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.21">Poppy, the Industrial Designer, will be looking at the working design of the remote.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.22">Tara, the Interface Designer, will be researching the technical functions.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.23">Heather, the project manager, is planning the next meeting.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.24">I, the Marketing Expert, will be researching specific user requirements.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.25">All of us should be brainstorming remote control ideas based on research and personal experience.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2015aME.pdecisions.1">
   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2015aME.s.26">Remote we design will be original, trendy and user friendly .</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.27">We are aiming for a 100 percent profit margin (production cost of 12.50 Euros, sale price of 25 Euros).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.28">Animals can be beautiful, friendly, noble, independent, good defenders, symbolic.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.29">Animals are good.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.30">We aim to make a great deal of money with this product by creating something unique and user-friendly (50 million Euros=3Dgoal).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.31">We hope to have a design in-place by our last meeting.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2015aME.pproblems.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.32">Creating a remote that is both internationally appealing and unique.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.33">Producing a product that is unique, user-friendly, internationally marketable for only 12.50 Euros: will we be able to do all we want?</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015aME.s.34">It was remarked that remotes may have different electronic specifications in different countries.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
