<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2012cID.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2012cID.s.1">Project manager opened meeting with summery of last meeting.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2012cID.s.2">Industrial designer gave presentation.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2012cID.s.3">Group discussed type of chips needed and wether or not we should keep the voice activation aspect of the remote.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2012cID.s.4">Interface desginer gave presentation, group discussed the general shape of remote and type of buttons/scrolls to use.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2012cID.s.5">Marketing desginer gave presentation and group finalized ideas on materials and chanagable covers.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2012cID.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2012cID.s.6">Project manager - prepare notes from last meeting, prepare outline for next meeting.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2012cID.s.7">Marketing - continue researching what people want to see in their remote and ways to make it fashionable.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2012cID.s.8">Designers - play with playdo.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2012cID.pdecisions.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2012cID.s.9">Voice recognition - group voted to keep voice recogniciton even though it means using custom chips.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2012cID.s.10">Changable covers - group reaffirmed commitment to changable covers which make remote into fashion item, allows for changes in fashion over the years, keeps people buying RR products.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2012cID.s.11">Battery - decided to use a long term battery for the "lifetime" of the remote.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2012cID.pproblems.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2012cID.s.12">Voice recognition - some debate over keeping the voice recogntion feature, would envolve using custom chips, however, it was decided to keep the future so that the remote could be technologically inovative.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2012cID.s.13">Buttons - what types of buttons to use??</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2012cID.s.14">Was decided to use a combination of buttons and scroll things for channel and volume control (respectively).</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
