<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2010bID.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.1">The meeting was a summary of the information aquired by each member of the team with regard to the specific design requirements of the remote.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.2">We have discovered that the company does not want us to design a unviersal remote but rather a remote specifically for TV.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.3">This changes the initial design requirements.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.4">We have since discussed the various functions of the remote and how we would like it to look.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.5">Our target audience was also discussed and we have decided on a universal quality.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.6">The design is to be kept simple and include the company logo.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2010bID.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.7">I need to investigate the main components of the remote and present my findings at the next meeting.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2010bID.pdecisions.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.8">All age ranges.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.9">Little to no techical ability required.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.10">Functions:</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.11">On/Off, volume up/down, channel up/down, mute, etc.   - Logo will be small and at the bottom of the remote.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.12">An ability to be found by the user when lost.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.13">Potential for a base instead of simple battery power.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.14">Large buttons.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.15">Menu option for more complex functions like closed captioning, subtitles, etc.   - voice activation functions.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2010bID.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.16">We have not decided on our power source.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.17">I think that a base would be a good idea for voice activation functions etc.   - the company colour isn't exactly great so we cannot make the whole of the remote that colour.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2010bID.s.18">Prices for materials to create this??</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
