<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2013dUI.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2013dUI.s.1">Firstly we covered the minutes from last meeting, and then the 2 designers presented their prototypes.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013dUI.s.2">These were 2 very similar models but embodied the options we hadnt decided on yet: whether to be round and smooth or banana-shaped, and whether to be hard plastic or softer rubber.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013dUI.s.3">There were also two different options of button 'compass point' so we had to discuss them. we then evaluated the product in terms of all the categories of style and function, practicality and cost. it was all satisfactory.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2013dUI.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2013dUI.s.4">Ummm. meetings finished.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013dUI.s.5">Make product!!</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2013dUI.pdecisions.1">
    <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2013dUI.s.6">Material: plastic is cheaper bhut even rubber was well within our price boundaries .   see excel spreadsheet for details.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013dUI.s.7">Product is bright yellow with black buttons, reflecting company colours.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013dUI.s.8">Implies banana shape but isnt specifically a banana.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013dUI.s.9">Push buttons in a simple 'compass point' setting with enter button and menues on screen.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2013dUI.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2013dUI.s.10">The 'trendiness' issue isnt complately addressed because the product isnt explicitly fruit themed although it does imply abstracted organic forms.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013dUI.s.11">We didnt know enough about programming to be able to know exactly about the menue on-screen television programming.. but just follow existing sky-cable technology.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
