<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2014dME.pabstract.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.1">The design team entered the room and presented the plasticine mock-up of the product.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.2">The design was simple and easily-explained.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.3">I was there to lead the product evaluation against the market research criteria.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.4">This became a bit confused, and we started talking about the finance of the product before we had evaluated it.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.5">I had to drag the meeting back to evaluation, and we came up with a score for the product.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.6">Then we had to refer to finance, and found that the product was over-budget.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.7">We considered the options, compared them to finance and the evaluation criteria, changed options, and then re-evaluated to find a product with a good evaluation score that met the budget.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2014dME.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.8">That was the last meeting.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.9">Phew.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2014dME.pdecisions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.10">We decided the product scored 1.8 on the evaluation scale.</sent><sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014dME.s.11">.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.12">The product came in over budget at 13.7 euros, and we decided to midify some features to bring it in under budget.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.13">We did away with the rubber case, but were able to incorporate an extra colour and another fruit-shaped button and remain within budget.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.14">This meant that we didn't lose any points on the fanciness and fashion evaluation.</sent><sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014dME.s.15">.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.16">We decided this maintained the product's innovation, ease of use, and corporate identity evaluation scores.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2014dME.pproblems.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.17">The project manager did not lead us through the agenda, so we became confused between whether to deal with finance before or after evaluating the product as presented by the designers.</sent><sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014dME.s.18">.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.19">I was not sure exactly how to evaluate the product based on the criteria I had devised, and my explanation of it was a little confused.</sent><sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014dME.s.20">.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014dME.s.21">We had a little trouble deciding which features to keep and which to do away with, but in the end I though we were satisfied with the result.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
