<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2010bME.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2010bME.s.1">We are steadily moving in the direction of actual product design.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2010bME.s.2">As compared to the first meeting, each member of the team seems to be more aware of the current situation in the "remote control world" and each is enthusiastic with our potential results.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2010bME.s.3">The meeting assessed what further research we must do and emphasized that there are still unclear issues to be addressed concerning consumer wants and needs.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2010bME.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2010bME.s.4">PM: compile meeting minutes, keep up morale, make sure group knows where project is headed.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2010bME.s.5">ID: address components concept of remote.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2010bME.s.6">UID: user interface concept research.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2010bME.s.7">ME: i must compile data on current trends within the market.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2010bME.pdecisions.1">
    <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2010bME.s.8">buttons to include:  power, channel, volume, numbers, menu.      menu to include options such as subtitles etc. volume/channel buttons to double as menu selection buttons.</sent>     <sent nite:id="ES2010bME.s.9">Power function addressed: use a power source other than AA or AAA, possible a charger base?</sent>     <sent nite:id="ES2010bME.s.10">NOT mulitifunctional, TV use only.</sent>     <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2010bME.s.11">assume consumers have little technical background, easy to use design needed, simple functions.</sent>     <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2010bME.s.12">color scheme of remote to include company colors and logo.  must promote our company!</sent>    <sent nite:id="ES2010bME.s.13">Include some sort of speech recognition?</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2010bME.s.14">Homing device?</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2010bME.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2010bME.s.15">Some areas unclear in powerpoint presentations.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2010bME.s.16">some terms unfamiliar on the website (ie RSI)- should be clearer to group members.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2010bME.s.17">Difficulties in defining speech recognition needs.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
