<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2013bME.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.1">This meeting involved the introduction of some new requirements from the Project Manager, specifically that this is only a television remote, that teletext technology is no longer cutting edge and to maintain the branding of Real Reaction in the handset.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.2">Then, there were three presentions dealing with some of the finer details of the project.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.3">I introduced information on consumer satisfaction with current remotes and suggestions for reducing the buttons.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.4">The User Designer introduced the remotes produced by the competition and the Industrial Designer brought up the basics that the remote needed for functionality.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.5">We also discussed keeping within the production costs and reducing buttons for ease of use.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.6">Finally, we mused on the need for more information about who makes purchasing decisions for televisions.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2013bME.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.7">Project Manager: organize the next meeting and keep the team in touch with new product developments.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.8">Industrial Designer: Focus on new constraints.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.9">User Designer: Deal with reduced button needs.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.10">Marketing Expert: Trend Watch.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2013bME.pdecisions.1">
  <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.11">What keys are important.</sent><sent import="high" nite:id="ES2013bME.s.12">.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.13">What the basic function of the remote should be.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.14">This is only a t.v. remote.</sent>
  <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.15">Keep the branding in mind for the user design.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2013bME.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.16">There were no problems except perhaps a lack of information.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013bME.s.17">Our discussions often raised issues we didn't have the information to directly answer.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
