<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2012aUI.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.1">The meeting discussed how to market a new remote control when there are already a significant number of remote controls on the market.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.2">The group discussed what was needed in a remote control, such as function and design, to make it user friendly, trendy, cost effective, and original.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.3">The price was discussed, as well as ideas about how to make it original.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.4">All group members contributed ideas about what they look for in a remote control, and what could be done to make this one original and different.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.5">The group discussed different marketing strategies, and what needed to be done to the product to make consumers say "I want it!"</sent>  
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2012aUI.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.6">Project manager- direct meeting, follow schedule.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.7">Market researcher-discuss any holes in the market, how to best market the product internationally.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.8">UI Designer- discuss design for product, how to make it unusual.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.9">Ind Designer- discuss what materials to use on the product, how to make it cost effective and functional.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2012aUI.pdecisions.1">
  <sent nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.10">Make prduct original.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.11">make product different from other remote controls on the market (different appearance).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.12">Make it obvious how product works (user friendly).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.13">Cost.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.14">make product easy to use, such as using lighted buttons.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.15">new ideas for remote controls such as inter-changeable face plates.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2012aUI.pproblems.1">
    <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2012aUI.s.16">how to make product different than those already on the market.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
