<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2014cID.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2014cID.s.1">We discussed the various options we face regarding each aspect of the remote control.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014cID.s.2">This included more technical aspects of the design including he power supply and tecnology used inside, the practical aspects of the design such as the way the buttons may be labelled and finally the aesthetic design and how the product may be marketed.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014cID.s.3">For my particular area we were able to establish the fundamental components required for the design and I now know what will be incorporated into my part of the remote control.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2014cID.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2014cID.s.4">Both designers will be making a prototype model of the remote control and the market designer will be looking more at how the product will be marketed.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cID.s.5">The project leader will probably be thinking about how the aspects will come together for the next meeting (but i'm not entirely sure).</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2014cID.pdecisions.1">
  <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014cID.s.6">A standard rubber casing - with a single curve and rubber buttons - to fit the current and hopefully future trends.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cID.s.7">+ linked to the above to use the simplest and cheapest circuit board.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cID.s.8">To keep the design simple enough - and to make sure all the buttons are clearly marked and easy to interpret.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cID.s.9">To use a kinetic - not a standard battery - power supply.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2014cID.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2014cID.s.10">Trying to decide in a short space of time which aspects of the design people prefered.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cID.s.11">Discussing some issues for too long and others not for long enough.</sent>    <sent nite:id="ES2014cID.s.12">A lack of direction in the meetings.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
