<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2014bID.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2014bID.s.1">We dicussed the various aspects of the project including the way the system works, functions on the remote and also the visual design and the market we are aiming for.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014bID.s.2">Ie. what people want, what we are planning to give them and how it will work.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014bID.s.3">Most important to myself as the industrial designer was what functions we are going to have in the remote as I have to design the system that will incorporate them.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2014bID.pactions.1">

   <sent nite:id="ES2014bID.s.4">Project Manager- minutes.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bID.s.5">Myself- industrial designer - working out how the remote will work with the functions selected.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bID.s.6">User-interface designer - working more on the design of the product.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bID.s.7">Marketing - finding prices(?) - more info on the market.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2014bID.pdecisions.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2014bID.s.8">To try and reach the broadest possible market.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bID.s.9">To look into the possibility of having a voice recognition or 'clapper' system for people to find lost remotes with.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014bID.s.10">To make the product as simple as possible to use.</sent>    <sent nite:id="ES2014bID.s.11">To have two seperate groups of buttons - basic channel and volume buttons on the front and tuning, visual adjustment and other required but often less used buttons hidden away.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2014bID.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2014bID.s.12">Agreeing on whether to use a voice recognition system or not.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bID.s.13">Agreeing on exactly which buttons to incorporate.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014bID.s.14">Not knowing at this point exactly what will be possible give the time and financial restrictions (lack of info).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bID.s.15">Maybe a lack of organisation as to what is expected of each of us before the next meeting.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
