<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2003bME.pabstract.1">
  <sent nite:id="ES2003bME.s.1">There was a good discussion.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2003bME.s.2">People shared their views and management was sure and steadfast in making decisions and sticking to them.</sent>  
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2003bME.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2003bME.s.3">The marketting person should make the product more relevant to a particular audience.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2003bME.s.4">The interface person should choose some designs and prepare to show examples to everybody.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2003bME.s.5">The industrial engineer should prepare more data on energy constraints and give examples of what is available given the constraints that are in place.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2003bME.s.6">The manager should anticipate choices people are gonna make and way up the pros and cons in advanced.</sent> 

</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2003bME.pdecisions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2003bME.s.7">The remote would control the television alone.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2003bME.s.8">There would be no voice recognition given the power constraints .</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2003bME.s.9">There would be a small number of buttons to control the remote.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2003bME.s.10">There would be a localizer for the remote... that is something that will alert the user where the remote is to be found, in the event that the remote is lost.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2003bME.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2003bME.s.11">I was considered as to which audience the product would be targetted at...</sent> <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2003bME.s.12">I feel aproduct that is not tailored specific for a group is unlikely to achieve wide spread commericial success.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
