<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2009bUI.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.1">The meeting went over quite smoothly,   The project manager was able to run the meeting effectively and some good ideas were brought forward.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.2">I was dissapointed that the manager didn't specifically delineate who was doing what... basically what the decisions were and how they were to be carried out.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.3">Each of the individuals I believe were generally satisfied with the meeting and as interface designer I feel confident in the direction we are heading in.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2009bUI.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.4">Marketing - do we actually have a market for the product we are talking about?</sent>                   <sent nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.5">Start thinking about the target group and how we are going to reach out to them.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.6">Manager - keep the team on track.</sent>                   <sent nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.7">Ensure next meeting is productive and ready to be executed effectively.</sent>                   <sent nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.8">Make clear during the next meeting what each members tasks are after the next meeting (set out clear goals).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.9">Industrial Designer - work out how device will work, what functions are required, etc...                               - confirm components, technology.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.10">User Interface Designer - work out how the user will work the device, and give it some distinct features as a selling point.</sent>                                       <sent nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.11">Work out logic of device (from a user standpoint).</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2009bUI.pdecisions.1">
    <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.12"> hard plastic casing.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.13">Black and red colours.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.14">Use the logo "we put fashion into electronics"   do not use "teletext"   build in a voice recognition feature!</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.15"> ensure we must seek to have a final production cost of ?12.50.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2009bUI.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2009bUI.s.16">Is the product really viable in the framework we have put together?</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
