<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2008cPM.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.1">This meeting was the most productive one we have had so far.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.2">Each team member had received a large amount of information and processed it very well.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.3">Individual presentations were very useful and informative.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.4">Contributions made from each team member added new elements that added information about what our objectives and goals should be.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.5">We were a little pressed for time because of the large number of options and amount of information.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.6">There was a very pleasing group atmosphere where we not only informed one another, but also laughed with one another.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.7">We achieved all that we needed to, and I am very hopeful about finding the solution to this project.</sent>  
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2008cPM.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.8">All will put powerpoint in the shared folders.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.9">ID and UID will make a clay model.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.10">Marketing will do product evaluation.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.11">PM will put minutes in shared folder.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2008cPM.pdecisions.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.12">Energy source will be a kinetic battery.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.13">Use a simple chip.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.14">Case out of latex/rubber and curved.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.15">Use fruity colors for case (fashion).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.16">Push buttons (as few as possible)- only 8/9.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.17">On television screen menu for additional functions.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2008cPM.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.18">Too much information for the time period.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.19">Marketing expert disagreed with findings of marketing research.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.20">Didn't know difference between latex and rubber.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.21">Small debate over whether to have a scroll button or not.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008cPM.s.22">Some time management issues- there is not a clock in the room, and i can't see computer clock when i am using the powerpoint presentation.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
