<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2015bUI.pabstract.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.1">The meeting was well laid out and better planning was obvious in everyone's presentatio.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.2">The project manager was good at keeping the discussion goinng.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.3">Everyone contributed well to the meeting and the ideas and issues that were raised were interrsting and useful.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2015bUI.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.4">The next meeting is concerned with more specific designs and features of the remote control.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.5">The project manager will continue to lead discussion.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.6">The ID will look at more specific design materials that will make the remote economically and functionally viable.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.7">The UID will concentrate on the design of the remote and how its features are presented.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.8">The ME will see if our ideas are sellable on an international market and whether they will appeal to our target group of 20-30 year olds.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2015bUI.pdecisions.1">
  <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.9">Decisions:   single function remote.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.10">Disreguard teletexr.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.11">Nod lcd screen.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.12">Must incorporate company logo and colours.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.13">Target group 20 - 30.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.14">10-15 second light upp when buttons are used.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.15">RR symbol lights up as well.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.16">Remote can be personalised - interchangable covers.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.17">Minimise buttons
  alarm which can be adhered to TV set.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2015bUI.pproblems.1">
  <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.18">Did not have time to discuss battery issues.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.19">Time was limited so not all issues were sufficiently discussed and resolves.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bUI.s.20">Decisions were sometimes made before all participants had their say.   some of the issues were not definitely resolved and I'm unsure of some of the exact decisions.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
