<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2008dME.pabstract.1">

   <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.1">In our last meeting, we looked at 3 prototype options, evaluated if the selected option conformed to the criteria of remotes we established earlier, checked that our costs met the company requirement and reflected on the technology and group dynamics of the day.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.2">Three design options (the rhombus, the potato/mango, the martian) were shared with the group.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.3">We decided to use the potato, and added a sixth button to the front (much like a Ninendo game piece) for power to prevent using the menu button for two tasks.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.4">We then used the white board to make sure that the remote was acceptable in the following categories: fancy look-and-feel, functional look-and-feel, technological innovation, easy-to-use, spongy, fruit &amp; vegetable considerastion, matches behaviour appropriately, addresses RSI concerns, easy to learn, won't lose, simple, fashionable, meets target audience, incorporates company logo/colors.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.5">We kept costs under 12.5 euros and decided to stick with the design.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2008dME.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.6">None.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2008dME.pdecisions.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.7">Kinetic battery.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.8">6 buttons.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.9">Potato/mango shape.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.10">Yellow/other color options for interface.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.11">Latex material.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.12">No roaming device.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.13">Single curved.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2008dME.pproblems.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.14">Money, had to adjust costs a bit.   deciding on roaming/lost feature.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008dME.s.15">Not knowning what some features were (aka single/double curve).</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
