<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2014bME.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.1">The two designers and the marketing manager presented their resarch competently and clearly.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.2">My marketing presentation brought information to the project about what people use and what people find annoying about a remote control which had an influence over the final design.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.3">The industrial designer presented the workings of a remote control, and the user interface designer presented information on what makes remote controls user-friendly.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.4">The project manager reminded us of some information that had been passed to him by the management - that the time to market must be small, and that the design should incorportate the company logo and colour.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2014bME.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.5">The design team will investigate the configuration of buttons on the rear panel, and present reccommendations.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.6">The design team will come up with a specific design based on the decisions made about the functions we want on the remote.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.7">The project manager will summarise the last meeting and devise an agenda for the next meeting.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.8">The project manager will keep us informed of any decisions from the management.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.9">The marketing manager will investigate whether people like the design of the remote we have decided on.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2014bME.pdecisions.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.10">The project manager promised to communicate company directives to the workers when he received them, rather than at meetings, so we could plan effectively.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.11">We decided that as losing the remote is a major annoyance, we would put a hand-clap recognition function into it.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.12">There will be no teletext function as this is not used much now because of the internet.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.13">Because some buttons are used more often than others, there will be the important buttons on the front and less-often-used buttons on the back, under a panel.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.14">The front panel buttons are 16 in number - numbers 0-9, volume +/-, mute, power, channel +/-   We decided on a few buttons for the rear panel - brightness and contrast, tuning +/- and 'confirm' - and decided to do more resarch on audio and picture adjustment buttons.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2014bME.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.15">The project manager told us a couple of pieces of information that he maybe should have told us before the meeting - this is more important for the design team than me.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.16">I should have taken time to email those design-specific aspects of the market resarch to the design team, so they could maybe adjust their presentations to take account of them.</sent><sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014bME.s.17">.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014bME.s.18">Perhaps I should have done my presentation first, as it's important to show what the customer wants before designing.</sent><sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014bME.s.19">.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
