<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2003aME.pabstract.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.1">Meeting was interesting as an introduction.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.2">It is now easy to remember everybody as I remember their favourite animals but I do not remember their names.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.3">Goal was well specified and target of 50M euro was specified.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.4">It was good that we had an opportunity to express our ideas in the meeting.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2003aME.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.5">Project leader should probably take a look at all of the ideas that were expressed and some how way up the pros and cons of each one... especially with the number of units we would like to sell and the budget that we have.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.6">Marketing expert will have to actually decide what people want and if it is feasible to give the people what they want.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.7">What audience will be targetted and expected return from target audience.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.8">Interface designer will have to wait until the requirements are in before he can really design the interface.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.9">However, some features are common to all remote controls.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.10">He can begin designing those features or deciding whether the remote will be so radical that even the most basic features are done away with.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.11">Industrial engineer will have to consider which materials are available at the given price.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.12">Also, engineer will have to wait for requirements as the use of the remote will determine which material.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.13">For example, a nice soft material may be great for attracting a certain audience, but if the remote is to be used for long periods of time, daily, then the soft material may simply wear away quicker.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.14">A more sturdy remote would be more appropriate.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.15">However, if the remote is to be used as conventional remotes are used, then the sturdyness is nnecessary.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.16">Please note that I have never come across a soft remote but was just using it as an example.</sent>

</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2003aME.pdecisions.1">
    <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2003aME.s.17">Functionality was discussed.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.18">Physical features were also discussed.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2003aME.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2003aME.s.19">Insufficient time for everybody to give an idea so best idea up until end of meeting was probably idea everyone went away with.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
