<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2008aPM.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.1">This was a very introductory meeting.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.2">We focused mainly on getting to know each other and doing a little bit of brainstorming about the project.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.3">It was the first time learning to use the tools, so we were all a bit apprehensive, but very willing to try.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.4">I used a powerpoint presentation to give project aims, including finances, and then proceeded into a brainstorm about what we would each like in a television remote control.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.5">Everyone participated fully and seemed engaged in the discussion.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.6">A highly successful introductory meeting.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2008aPM.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.7">Learn more about specific roles.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.8">Project manager will create minutes, send out email with powerpoint and minutes attached.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.9">Others will brainstorm, according to directive from their personal coach.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2008aPM.pdecisions.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.10">Not a particularly decision-heavy meeting.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.11">Introductions, objective to work as a team.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.12">Emphasis on filling specific roles, and then collaborating.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.13">Certain agreements on what we want in the project.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.14">practical features:  keep the remote simple, with large buttons.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2008aPM.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.15">Lack of information.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.16">We weren't sure whether the project is for a general remote, or specifically television.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.17">We were unsure of our roles as yet (i don't think it will be a problem later).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2008aPM.s.18">None of us are particularly talented artists, so drawing was a bit difficult...</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
