<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2016aUI.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2016aUI.s.1">The meeting perhaps could have been constructed a little better with more use of the powerpoint presentation and the structure laid out in it.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016aUI.s.2">We perhaps went too quickly in to the topic of discussion and should better have used the first meeting as a more general meeting.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016aUI.s.3">However, the ideas being passed around were interesting.</sent><sent nite:id="ES2016aUI.s.4">I felt that i made my initial ideas on concept and design early in the meeting and that they were listened to and appreciated.</sent><sent nite:id="ES2016aUI.s.5">I tried to concentrate on the design element and how we could make it unique.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016aUI.s.6">The industrial designer did his role well i felt looking into the logistics and weakness of my initial idea.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016aUI.s.7">The project manager could have had perhaps more control and a position of more authority.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2016aUI.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2016aUI.s.8">To produce and prepare presentations on their roles and their findings.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016aUI.s.9">Marketing to research product, myself to look at technical fucntions of remote.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016aUI.s.10">Not entirely sure what everyone is doing because wasn't made clear in the meeting.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2016aUI.pdecisions.1">
    <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2016aUI.s.11">Ultimately to make easy to use, durable remote with a unique design.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2016aUI.pproblems.1">
    <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2016aUI.s.12">Suggested that should make a universal remote control  this is too complex a product i believe.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2016aUI.s.13">Finish with clear goals and conclusions and the next step outlined.</sent><sent import="high" nite:id="ES2016aUI.s.14">.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
