<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2002bME.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2002bME.s.1">We have just completed a 30 minute meeting, the second of our project team which is in the early stages of planning a new television remote control product.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2002bME.s.2">This meeting was an opportunity for product features, market trends and user preferences to be reviewed.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2002bME.s.3">Each member brought relevant information to the meeting in which the goal was for a decision to be made on the target market group (demographic), the product features and the general design concept.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2002bME.s.4">As a team we attempted to use all available information to make the best possible plan as to the project plan.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2002bME.s.5">Due to various limitation and ambiguities, some decisions were made as matter of speed and group decision irrespective of available information.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2002bME.pactions.1">

</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2002bME.pdecisions.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2002bME.s.6">It was decided that the product would be marketed to an international 15-35 age group.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2002bME.s.7">that the product would be tailored to a high-end product position in the market relative to price, design, but not necessarily to features being overly high-tech.   that the design would aim to be simplified and extra features concealed.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2002bME.s.8">That features would be organised relative to 1. audio 2. video features and 3 device controls.</sent>    <sent nite:id="ES2002bME.s.9">Device controls would place frequent controls in a most accessible position.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2002bME.s.10">A goal of the design concept would be to produce an ergonomic, styled product keeping in synch with the company values and project aims.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2002bME.pproblems.1">
 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
