<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2014cME.pabstract.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.1">I presented trends in fashion and asked whether we could incorporate them in the design of the product.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.2">I was not convinced myself that some of the trends were desirable to incorporate, and the group confirmed this.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.3">The industrial designer told us about the options for the components for the remote, and what his preferences were.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.4">The user interface designer showed us a few remotes and possible niche markets for remotes, and that we should avoid ambiguity in button design.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.5">The project manager suggested we make decisions after each presentation, but in the end we made our final decisions after the three presentations.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2014cME.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.6">I will be focussing on the product evaluation - what do people think of the design we have come up with?</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.7">The design team will be building a prototype out of plasticine to show us at the next meeting.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.8">The project manager will be going through the minutes and formulating an agenda for the next meeting.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2014cME.pdecisions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.9">We decided on various design aspects.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.10">The remote should be a single curve, for sleekness.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.11">It should be powered kinetically.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.12">It should have rubber buttons and a rubber case.</sent><sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014cME.s.13">.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.14">There should be voice recognition - but just to find the remote, not for functions.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.15">The standby button should be fashonable - probably in the shape of an apple, and red in colour.</sent><sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014cME.s.16">.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.17">The other buttons should be a simple shape, with simple labels.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2014cME.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.18">The project manager got tied up in typing up the minutes and couldn't give a proper presentation.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.19">The fashion trends that I found were somewhat ridiculous, and I felt a bit silly presenting them.</sent><sent import="high" nite:id="ES2014cME.s.20">.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.21">It was unclear what component options were compatible with which circuit board - i.e. did the voice recognition require a more advanced circuit?</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cME.s.22">Issues came up which would have influenced previous meetings - the distinctions between the meetings feel a little arbitrary.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
