<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2004aPM.pabstract.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.1">This was the first meeting of our team, a new project was introduced - the ddesign, manufacture and distribution of a new remote control.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.2">We talked for the first time and became better aquainted with eachother through an extra task - drawing pictures of animals and each talkiing about them.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.3">We concluded the meeting with a brief discussion about our project and what we want to get out of it; key features we think are important and design concerns.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.4">We also discussed our budget and how that could affect our plans for the product.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2004aPM.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.5">The industrial designer will look at what the product needs to do, functionality.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.6">The User interface designer will look into materials and the processes involved in the making of our product.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.7">The marketing expert will look at the markets at the moment to try and identify any pitfalls, and niches.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2004aPM.pdecisions.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.8">1) We decided upon a 'universal control' one handset for all your t.v. and video equiptment.</sent><sent import="high" nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.9">.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.10">2) It is important that the product is accessable to a wide age-range of consumers.</sent> <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.11">.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.12">3) We decided that it was important to reflect the company's image in our product, 'We put the fasion in electronics' .</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.13">4) Our budget will affect the specific design of the product, we want it to look trendy but not expensive to produce - silver plastic etc.   5) We want the control to look uncluttered and undaunting to the consumer.</sent> <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.14">.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.15">6) A flip open design was discussed, which would reduce the size of the control.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.16">7) An electronic panel should be inside for further features such as teletext, programming and sound functions.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2004aPM.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.17">1) Our design aim, being trendy and upmarket might clash with our budget - this is to be discussed at a later date.</sent> <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.18">.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2004aPM.s.19">2) We don't want to alienate 'older' consumers with the use of too much technology in our product.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
