<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2015aUI.pabstract.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2015aUI.s.1">The meeting was well structured and the project manager did her job well.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aUI.s.2">It would have been better if we had more time to prepare but I think that everyone did well in their roles.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aUI.s.3">The discussion was a bit short and not much information was exchanged, that is the main negative point.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2015aUI.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2015aUI.s.4">Each member will present their ideas based on the role they have been given.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aUI.s.5">The project manager will lead the meeting.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aUI.s.6">The ID will present ideas on the working design.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aUI.s.7">The UIDwill present ideas on the technical functions design and the ME will give insight into the remote control market.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2015aUI.pdecisions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2015aUI.s.8">We decided that the remote control should be trendy but also cost effective.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aUI.s.9">We decided that it needs to have a universal design so that it can be sold internationally.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aUI.s.10">We also decided that it cannot be boring but stand out from the rest in an original way.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2015aUI.pproblems.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2015aUI.s.11">Everyone was slightly unprepared but managed well under the circumstances.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aUI.s.12">I do not think that everyone got to read through all the information that was given before the meeting.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015aUI.s.13">The questionaire took up most of our time before the meeting, leaving us ill prepared.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
