<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2013aUI.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2013aUI.s.1">The project manager coherently and succintly explained our objectives and confirmed our roles with us.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013aUI.s.2">The meeting was a success in that we each had an opportunity to gain an insight into each others' mind: with the drawing animals and listing characteristics.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013aUI.s.3">After this we discussed the job in hand; including budgeting and marketing which although not specific to my role is still useful to consider, when choosing materials and such.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013aUI.s.4">We then had a very useful brainstorming session where we thought aloud about various ideas of what we wanted from a remote control, and possible styles.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2013aUI.s.5">We all seem to be consistent in wanting one that is simple and functional, easy to use with no extraneous functions, but also modern looking and stytlish: bright colours, big buttons, along the lines of an Ipod rather than a traditional remote control.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2013aUI.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2013aUI.s.6">Marketing member: look at worth and price of relevant materials and compare with industrial designer which materials are best.   industrial designer: think about next steps.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013aUI.s.7">User-interface: consider functions, buttons.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2013aUI.pdecisions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2013aUI.s.8">*divide tasks and report back at next meeting
  *conduct individual research, for me concentrating on what functions are absolutely necessary and which can be discarded (following on from discussion where we decided that most remotes have far too many useless buttons.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2013aUI.s.9"> for me, look at existing remotes, compare and contrast.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2013aUI.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2013aUI.s.10">Must not cost too much to produce - remember profit margins.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2013aUI.s.11">Possible we might concentrate too much on style and not on important functional matters.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
