<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2009cUI.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.1">The meeting went over quite smoothly,   we decided to move away from the touch screen concept and strictly move to a voice control system with simple console for major functions.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.2">Combining a flip back mechanism to access more advanced features.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.3">We also will have a changeable faceplate and are playing with the idea of a non-standard shape to the control.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2009cUI.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.4">Marketing - not sure!!</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.5">Manager - keep the team on track.</sent>                   <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.6">Ensure next meeting is productive and ready to be executed effectively.</sent>                   <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.7">Make clear during the next meeting what each members tasks are after the next meeting (set out clear goals).</sent>                   <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.8">Take directions from his "personal coach"   Industrial Designer - work out how device will work, what functions are required, etc...                               - confirm components, technology.</sent>                               <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.9">Work with user interface designer on prototype.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.10">User Interface Designer - work on design interface always considering end user.</sent>                                       <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.11">Work out logic of device (from a user standpoint).</sent>                                       <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.12">Work with Industrial designer on prototype.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2009cUI.pdecisions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.13">Several casing styles: wood type, spongy, hard plastic in the realm of "Apple" products, etc...   simple rubber buttons for most frequently used features and a flip back area to access advanced features.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.14">Voice control mechanism (much like on our current coffee maker system).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.15">Costs are able to rise slightly over budget.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2009cUI.pproblems.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.16">We've changed our direction a bit with the move away from a touch screen system.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009cUI.s.17">Incorporating the flip back advanced area into a sleek simple design.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
