<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2015dME.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.1">Our final meeting was half-an-hour long.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.2">Heather started things off, and then the prototype was presented.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.3">Poppy and Tara created a remote that is shaped like a small mango (taking off from the fashionable fruit trend) and the numbers are in a circle around it.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.4">It is easy to hold, unique and would come in many different colour schemes.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.5">After their presentation, I walked us through the marketing product evaluation.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.6">I came up with 11 questions based on the goals that we made for ourselves in the functional and conceptual meetings.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.7">The group discussed each question and decided on a score based on a scale of 1 to 7, where 1 is true and 7 is false.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.8">Our average score was 1.9, which is quite good (see Marketing- Final Evaluation in the Projects Folder) .</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.9">Heather presented the Finance report, and we were pleased to see that we were just below are allowable budget of 12.50 Euros at 12.20.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.10">Our final project evaluation was that we were succesful in creating a remote control that we believe will be welcomed by the public.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2015dME.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.11">It's out of our hands now.... we'll leave it up to the engineers!</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2015dME.pdecisions.1">
   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2015dME.s.12">Will replace the + sign in the middle of the ring of numbers with an Enter button .</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2015dME.s.13">Logo should be less glaring, either smaller or different colour .</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.14">We can implement different face plates later on if the remote is successful.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.15">The marketing scheme will have to stress the simplicity of the remote (only power, channel and volume buttons!).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.16">The marketing scheme will have to stress the efficiency of the kinetic energy source (be good to the environment and save money on batteries!).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.17">The marketing scheme will have to promote the trendiness of the product and emphasize the RR motto of "putting the fashion into electronics!"</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2015dME.pproblems.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.18">The buttons kept on falling off.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.19">The designers felt they lacked materials (more playdough colours would have been appreciated).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.20">The alarm is an interior aspect so we could not see it/evaluate it.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015dME.s.21">Never truly resolved the 'smart materials' environmental issue.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
