<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2009bME.pabstract.1">

 <sent nite:id="ES2009bME.s.1">Everyone gave a brief presentation on their current position with the remote after preliminary research.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009bME.s.2">Although our options for other non-telelvision based functions is out of the picture, my research showed a growing interest in voice technology and so we are pursing a touchscreen device with voice software capabilities.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009bME.s.3">Over all the meeting went well and everyone is on the same page as we pursue some specific design possibilities.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2009bME.pactions.1">
 <sent nite:id="ES2009bME.s.4">We are pursuing the touch screen , sleek but simple voice activated remote path. each team member will come back to the table with more specific design options, specifically i will be looking into the current trends in the remote industry.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2009bME.pdecisions.1">
  <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2009bME.s.5">Only television options .</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009bME.s.6">No recharging or docking options, therefore a cordless probably lithium battery option is our primary example.</sent> <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2009bME.s.7">Use compay colours, logo and slogan on boot up screen .</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009bME.s.8">No teleltext.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009bME.s.9">Plastic casing, sleek design.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009bME.s.10">Paging function with or without voice recognition is going to need a paging base for the television.</sent> <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2009bME.s.11">Primary function screen will be very basic .</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2009bME.pproblems.1">
  <sent nite:id="ES2009bME.s.12">Some of our primary interests in this design have been vetoed from above.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009bME.s.13">Some of our higher tech options are impossible because of cost and complexity being too much for the market.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
