<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2014cUI.pabstract.1">

   <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.1">The market research and design team made presentations, after each individual talk the merits of the findings were discussed and decisions were made.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.2">The industrial design presentation resulted in the decisions to use a simple circuit board, have kinetic power and have rubber button without the use of a scroll button.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.3">The companys speech recognition was discussed and it was decided that this would be used as a function to find lost remotes, and will not be connected to the signalling functions.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.4">The user-interface design confirmed that scroll buttons are not aesthetically pleasing, and highlighted the need for simplistic buttons.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.5">It was pointed out that there are specialist remotes, but that we are targeting a wider market and do not need to consider these.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.6">There is current speech technology for signalling that we do not want to compete with.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.7">Market research highlighted the need for sleek trendy remotes possibly with a fruit theme, and a spongey feel.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.8">Rubber casing will be used and the standby button will be an apple.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2014cUI.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.9">Project manager - write minutes, prepare presentation.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.10">Market research - continue researching trends, prepare presentation.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.11">Designers - make model of product.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2014cUI.pdecisions.1">
  <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.12">Kinetic power supply.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.13">Simple circuit board.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.14">Rubber case with single curve.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.15">Rubber bush button, no scroll button, red apple shaped standby button (other buttons simple shapes).</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.16">Company logo on sticker.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2014cUI.pproblems.1">
  <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.17">Don't have adequate information about the company logo design/colour scheme.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.18">Not sure about cost (packaging) implications of selling curved covers - probably not significant.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2014cUI.s.19">Don't want to make remote to trendy as will be redundant next year.   considered interchangeable rubber casing of different fun colours, but not sure about demand and manufacturing cost.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
