<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2007aUI.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2007aUI.s.1">Since I am the user interface designer, I saw the previous meeting as an opportunity to discuss very generally what the remote should do and how it should operate.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2007aUI.s.2">We very generally discussed layout designs and mentioned that there is a tension between wanting it to have comprehensive functionality but not to be too 'busy'.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2007aUI.s.3">By the end of the meeting we all seemed to agree that we should do a fairly simply remote in terms of functionality but to do it very well, for example to have an ergonomic design and buttons that are easy to understand.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2007aUI.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2007aUI.s.4">I am working on some general design ideas.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2007aUI.s.5">The marketing person is hopefully researching our target demographic.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2007aUI.s.6">The industrial designer has some overlap with what I am doing, so I think she will come to the next meeting with some overlapping design ideas.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2007aUI.s.7">The project manager should be writing the minutes of the last meeting and preparing the next meeting.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2007aUI.pdecisions.1">
    <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2007aUI.s.8">To have a simple but well-designed remote.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2007aUI.s.9">To have the industrial designer and user-interface designer work closely together.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2007aUI.s.10">To have a lock function on the remote.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2007aUI.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2007aUI.s.11">At first we seemed uncertain of whether the remote should work solely for the television or for all televison-related electronics.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2007aUI.s.12">The pacing of the meeting did not seem consistent.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2007aUI.s.13">We didn't make the best use of time.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
