<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2005aUI.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2005aUI.s.1">The meeting was primarily for me to introduce myself to the other team members and to start thinking about what factors I need to condiser for the next meeting.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2005aUI.s.2">My main function is to make the product attrcactive to potential buyers - make them want to buy our product because it is trendy, fashionable and ergonomic.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2005aUI.s.3">I suggested some kind of gimmick would be a good idea, for example, like a glow-in the dark remote or one that you can whistle at to find it.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2005aUI.s.4">Raj also put forward the importance of looking at other companies to see what they are doing.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2005aUI.s.5">It was also pointed out that the product had to remain cheap- selling at 25 euros and costing us 12.50 euros to make. from the meeting, my main role now is to come up with some ideas about shapes and colours for the product.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2005aUI.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2005aUI.s.6">All need to look on the internet etc for research into each of our next steps as decided in the descisions.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2005aUI.pdecisions.1">
  <sent nite:id="ES2005aUI.s.7">Decided our next moves for each roles.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2005aUI.s.8">Raj needs to look at competitors, .</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2005aUI.s.9">I need to look at shapes and colours that are fachionable.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2005aUI.s.10">And Arlo needs to look at materials.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2005aUI.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2005aUI.s.11">No problems concerning the productsome slight confusion (on my part) of whos function is it to look at costs and finance.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2005aUI.s.12">Thought it would be more for the marketing, but actually Arlo's role.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
