<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2009aME.pabstract.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2009aME.s.1">Although it is still early in the design process, I feel we are off to a good start.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009aME.s.2">We started off with a general over view of the project goals, design method and fiscal positioning and then gave a general ice-breaker and introduction to the other team members.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009aME.s.3">With the remaining time we managed to brainstorm some ideas for the new design - what we are looking for, some new directions we might be able to take and some innovative strategies to corner the market.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009aME.s.4">For my part I am interested to see what sort of fuctions we can cater the remote to for the greatest general appeal.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009aME.s.5">As television is a huge part of any demographic, we have the chance to come up with a profitable innovative design that could be used the world over.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2009aME.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2009aME.s.6">I'm looking into user requirements.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009aME.s.7">The designers are brainstorming function and design features, and we are all brainstorming concept elements and options for the remote.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009aME.s.8">At the next meeting we'll compare and get a better handle on what direction we are headed in.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2009aME.pdecisions.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2009aME.s.9">To brainstorm in all areas of design.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2009aME.s.10">To come back with some general guidelines about our goals with this product .</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009aME.s.11">To reconsider the final sale price of the remote and our profit margins.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2009aME.s.12">I personally will look into user requirements before our next meeting .</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2009aME.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2009aME.s.13">None really.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
