<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2015bME.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.1">Heather opened the meeting just after 12pm. Poppy gave a powerpoint presentation on the working design of our product.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.2">She spoke about the visibility of the remote, its 'findability' and the idea of creating a remote that has smart materials that allow for easy dismanteling, recycling and reusing.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.3">After Poppy, Tara gave her presentation regarding the technical functions of the remote, mainly whether it should be single-functional (just for TV) or multi-functional (for several electronica devices- DVD, CD, game consuls, etc).</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.4">Tara preferred single-functional.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.5">I gave the final presentation on the user requirement specs.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.6">I outlined the priorities of Real Remote (fashion, user friendly, effective) and went on to describe the findings of my market research and interviews.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.7">After this, Heather informed us of the decisions from management, namely, that it be single-functional, not use tele-text, incorporates company colour and logo.</sent>  <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.8">The meeting ended well, with the four participants coming to some important decisions based on our individual research.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.9">The most important decisions were that we will not use LCD or voice-recognition devices, we will have a minimum amount of buttons, an alarm system to find the remote and design buttons that are tactile and temporarily light-up.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.10">We briefly discussed the option of having various unique faceplates that the public could choose based on their personal preferences (compare to the current i-Pod marketing).</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2015bME.pactions.1">


</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2015bME.pdecisions.1">
   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2015bME.s.11">As per management executive decisions:   -remote will be single-functional: for TVs only .</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.12">We will not concern ourselves with teletext.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2015bME.s.13">The design will incorporate our logo and colour .</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.14">As result of meeting discussion and research sharing:   -buttons will be decipherable in the dark with use of tactile design.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2015bME.s.15">We will limit amount of buttons .</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.16">Agreed to avoid the glow-in-the-dark look due to tacky look, also not battery efficient if it's power-based.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2015bME.s.17">We agreed on a temporary light-up method, similar to the way cell phones light up when a button is touched .</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2015bME.s.18">Agree on alarm system: small paging system that can be stuck somewhere near/on TV.   -we will stick to our purpose of creating a simple, fashionable and user-friendly remote control .</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2015bME.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.19">Discussion on whether to put money into environmental research: Poppy spoke about smart materials that we could use, Heather was concerned about financial implications.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.20">We are to come to a decision soon.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2015bME.s.21">Only briefly discussed face-plate idea: we will need to do more research.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
