<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2006bUI.pabstract.1">

   <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.1">In this meeting the main issues concerning the functional design of the remote control were discussed.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.2">Group members reported on the current trends in the remote control technology including both design as well as technology issues.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.3">Our marketing manager gave us an overview of data reflecting user preferences.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.4">At this meeting the contribution I found most relevant to my role in the project was that of our marketing manager.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.5">Knowing what the trends are in what users expect will ahve a major influence in my making decisions about the interface design issues.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2006bUI.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.6">User Interface designer: Final decisions about the buttons we need and an initial design proposal.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.7">Technical designer: Estimate costs of incorporating the newest technology.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.8">Market manager:</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.9">More market research.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.10">Project manager: Plan for the next meeting.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2006bUI.pdecisions.1">
  <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.11">Remote will be used for TV only.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.12">We only incorporate the main function buttons: on/off, channels (both numbers and next/previous) and volume.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.13">Voice recognition as an extra.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.14">Targer group: age 15-35.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.15">Possibly supply a separate beeper button with the remote, to be attached on the TV set to allow to locate the position of the remote easily.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.16">Stylishness is very important.</sent>
  <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.17">Need to use our company colours and logo in the outer design.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2006bUI.pproblems.1">
  <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.18">We had some difficulties in projecting the presentations on the wall.</sent><sent import="high" nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.19">.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2006bUI.s.20">No other major difficulties this time.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
