<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2016bUI.pabstract.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.1">The meeting was very successful with each individual drawing well on their findings from their research and with each participant linking well and taking into account other people's info.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.2">I felt that my ideas were listened to and people contibuted on them constructively which allowed myself to develop my ideas with in the meeting environment.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.3">This meeting was perhaps more successful than the the previous meeting also.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2016bUI.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.4">The project manager was to prepare minutes on the last meeting and prepare for the next meeting.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.5">Industrial designer is to study the concept of the components necessary.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.6">User interface designer is to study user interface concept how consumer will use product.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.7">The marketing director is to research trends.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2016bUI.pdecisions.1">

  <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.8">To concentrate on the appearance and design of the remote.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.9">To design a remote for t.v use only.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.10">Further specifications were given of the colours and inclusion of the company motto.</sent> <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.11">A shape for the remote was decided upon  and came from an idea i had towards the close of the meeting.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.12">It was decided that the trends would ne investigated, components decided upon and whether it could be a two piece remote.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.13">The user interface should also be designed.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.14">The idea of speech recognition was to be dropped.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2016bUI.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.15">Problems were less during this meeting.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.16">The structure was clearer and the group agreed better on ideas.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.17">The feasibility and cost of the product was discussed so this could be taken into account.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016bUI.s.18">For my role the discussion and topic of which layout and what user interface would be my main aim for the next meeting.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
