<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2009cPM.pabstract.1">

   <sent nite:id="ES2009cPM.s.1">The four members of the team made brief presentations on what they had found through their research.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009cPM.s.2">Concepts for what the remote would be made of were dicussed as were considerations of cost, inclusion of advanced function, and voice recognition.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009cPM.s.3">It was ultimately concluded that we should design a small-sized remote control that was not of traditional remote control form that would include voice recognition technology.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2009cPM.s.4">The focus would be on simple function with the option of more advanced function.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2009cPM.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2009cPM.s.5">The UID and ID will develop a working prototype of the remote control.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009cPM.s.6">I will attempt to make a final decision on costs and benefits.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009cPM.s.7">The ME will provide information on market data.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2009cPM.pdecisions.1">
   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2009cPM.s.8">The touchscreen design was dropped in favour of voice recognition.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009cPM.s.9">The shape was decided to be non-remote like and built with rubber with 'gives' and multiple case colours.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2009cPM.s.10">An emphasis was placed on simple function to appease the majority of users with the option of advanced functions being limited.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2009cPM.pproblems.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2009cPM.s.11">No major issues were encountered, though I did fail to address some of the ideas presented when we opened the meeting up for discussion of various ideas.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
