<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2016cUI.pabstract.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.1">The meeting was a natural proggression from the previos meeting with all those doing research bringing new and relevant infromation to the table.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.2">There was perhaps too much influence from the designers and not enough from marketing director.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.3">However our conclusions and ideas to some extent have pre empted the findings from the research and our ideas have been ahead of the game.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.4">This includes the idea of speech recognition, the shape and concept of the remote.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.5">The influence of fruit on design could have been taken to literally with the predetermined company colours pointing us towards certain fruits and hence a certain product.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.6">However, we have come up with and devised a complex but yet unique design.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.7">It would be simple to use but perhaps costly to make.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.8">However, our roles have become clearer and we have devised something which should be unique.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2016cUI.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.9">Industrial designer and interface designer to decide upon a design and to model in clay.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.10">The marketing director to evalaute product.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.11">The project manager to over see and prepare for final meeting.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2016cUI.pdecisions.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.12">The energy source was decided upon.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.13">The colour.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.14">The shape.</sent> <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.15">The user interface was decided upon.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.16">The materials to be used.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2016cUI.pproblems.1">
    <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.17">Problems only arose from the discussion of the feasibility of design with certain materials.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2016cUI.s.18">These were discussed and resolved though in the meeting.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
