<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="ES2003cME.pabstract.1">
  <sent nite:id="ES2003cME.s.1">The physical appearance and functionality were discussed and agreed upon.</sent>     <sent nite:id="ES2003cME.s.2">Each person's task in preparation for the next meeting was handed out.</sent> <sent nite:id="ES2003cME.s.3">Ideas were discussed such as the physical material that the remote control should be made from and whether numbered buttons should be used or not.</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="ES2003cME.pactions.1">

  <sent nite:id="ES2003cME.s.4">Interface person and industrial person will work together to create a prototype of the physical product.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2003cME.s.5">The marketing person will decide how the next stage of evaluating the product will be conducted.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2003cME.s.6">The manager has to decide which person will have the greater influence at this stage.</sent>

</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="ES2003cME.pdecisions.1">
  <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2003cME.s.7">It was decided to have a rubber spongy type body for the remote control.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2003cME.s.8">There would be no buttons but the changing of channels will be menu driven.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2003cME.s.9">It was decided that there would be an underlying frame to the remot.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2003cME.s.10">It was also decided that the remote would be composed of "off the shelf" components.</sent> <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2003cME.s.11">It was hope that bulked buying would reduce the cost
  It was decided that the language for the menu for the remote should be configurable so that this remote could be used internationally... this widens the potential market.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="ES2003cME.pproblems.1">
  <sent nite:id="ES2003cME.s.12">Would it be feasible, given the limitations on cost, to have a USB connection with a programmable memory on board the remote.</sent>   <sent nite:id="ES2003cME.s.13">Fruit and veg may be fashionable but is it appropriate for a remote control.</sent>   <sent import="high" nite:id="ES2003cME.s.14">The target audience being those under the age of 60 since fashion is a key feature of the remote control.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
