<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="IS1001cPM.pabstract.1">
   <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.1">This was a conceptual design meeting in the framework of the remote control project.</sent>   <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.2">Industrial Designer presented conceptual specification of components, properties and materials
  and User Interface Designer presented conceptual specification of user interface.</sent> <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.3">Marketing expert.</sent>   <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.4">Gave an overview of the current trends.</sent>  <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.5">Decisions were taken jointly according to the presentations (see bellow).</sent> 
</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="IS1001cPM.pactions.1">
   <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.6">The Industrial Designer will work on the look-and-feel design and the User Interface Designer will work on the user-interface design, then both of them will work together on the first prototype.</sent> 
  <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.7">Marketing Expert will lead the product evaluation.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="IS1001cPM.pdecisions.1">
   <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.8">1.</sent> <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.9">Fancy aspect of the remote control is very important: according to current trend, we decided to make a remote control shaped as a banana (fruit shape things are trendy nowadays), moreover this is the color of our beloved company.</sent>   <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.10">Real Reaction.</sent> <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.11">The yellow color also ensure that the remote control will be easy to find.</sent>   <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.12">2.</sent> <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.13">The material of the remote control should be spongy: it is trendy and it makes the remote control more robust.</sent>   <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.14">So the remote control will be in a hard banana shaped case covered by a yellow spongy surface.</sent>   <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.15">3.</sent> <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.16">The wheel to change channel has been kept in our design: even if it introduces a cost increase, it also makes the remote control easy to use and innovative which are two important aspects for users.</sent>   <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.17">4.</sent> <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.18">The energy will be provided by standard batteries.</sent>   <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.19">5.</sent> <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.20">They were no specific problems related to chip on print.</sent> 
</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="IS1001cPM.pproblems.1">

  <sent nite:id="IS1001cPM.s.21">No specific problem at this stage.</sent> 
</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
