<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="IS1003bPM.pabstract.1">
<sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.1">The meeting offered to each participant to do a presentation on their views
on the remote control.</sent> <sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.2">Design requirements were discussed and some problems
were also discussed.</sent>
<sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.3">Each of the participants had the opportunity to present their opinion and
to make propositions.</sent>
<sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.4">The work that still has to be done has been dispatched between the
participants, according to their function.</sent>
<sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.5">Some questions are still opened to discussions, but the overall meeting was
constructive.</sent>
 
 
 
 
 
 

</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="IS1003bPM.pactions.1">
<sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.6">Presentation by each member of the team, according to their job of the
proposition for the remote control
Discussion about the functionalities and the overall look of the remote
control.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="IS1003bPM.pdecisions.1">
<sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.7">It was decided to create a fancy, easy-to-use remote control.</sent> <sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.8">The functions
has to be easily accessible, with as few buttons as possible.</sent>
<sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.9">David Jordan = User interface designer ( sophisticated functions, powerfull
and easy-to-use
Baba = Industrial designer proposed to use the international standards in
the sign choice: everyone will be able to understand these signs and it
will be more intuitive.</sent>
<sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.10">The industrial designer proposed to use the infrared technology: only
8euros per remote control to use this technology, and to have a wireless
remote control.</sent>
<sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.11">Florent Monay = Market expert: the remote control has to look fancy (75% of
users find it ugly), to be very simple to use, and take care of the health
of people as some functions are used intensively (zapping).</sent>
<sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.12">The choice of the colour for the remote control has to be the company
colour.</sent> <sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.13">The remote control must be associated to be company, through it
look and also through the slogan company.</sent>
<sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.14">It is why it has been decided to create a fancy and fashion remote control
with all the basic functions to interact with a television.</sent>  
 
 
 
  
 

</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="IS1003bPM.pproblems.1">
<sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.15">The problem of the ease of use of the remote control and the fact that it
has to be powerful has been discussed.</sent>
<sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.16">The question of the wireless or not wireless remote control is still opened
to further discussions.</sent>
<sent nite:id="IS1003bPM.s.17">The problem of the appearance of the remote control has to be taken into
account: proposition of a yellow line on the remote control, as the choice
of a personal colour will increase the price of the remote control.</sent>  
 
 
 

</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
