<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<nite:root xmlns:nite="http://nite.sourceforge.net/">
<participant_abstract nite:id="IS1008bPM.pabstract.1">

 <sent nite:id="IS1008bPM.s.1">Project Plan and Coordination.</sent> <sent nite:id="IS1008bPM.s.2">For new Remote Control.</sent>
 <sent nite:id="IS1008bPM.s.3">Introduce the team from different job functions on
Functional Design Plan and discussion on the subject
User Interface Plan and suggestion on the product and project
Sales and Marketing target plan and discussion to improve and introduce
some of new ideas on the product to make success in the market.</sent> 
 <sent nite:id="IS1008bPM.s.4">Management decision and plan about product and project features</sent>
 
 
 
 
 

</participant_abstract>
<participant_actions nite:id="IS1008bPM.pactions.1">

<sent nite:id="IS1008bPM.s.5">Christine with come up with added Functional design features and project
plan for this product
Agnes give feed back and opinion about new functional designproduct user
acceptance and quality
ED will come up with sales and marketing ideas
Sridhar will coordinate for whole project.</sent> <sent nite:id="IS1008bPM.s.6">To submit first draft version of
the product and project plan
Sridhar will coordinate to get some technical back or technical tie-up
better product features for the functional design
Sridhar will coordinate for budget discussion and project discussion about
the new features which is going to add.</sent>
<sent nite:id="IS1008bPM.s.7">Coordinating  with the project team for further discussions.</sent> 
</participant_actions>
<participant_decisions nite:id="IS1008bPM.pdecisions.1">
 <sent nite:id="IS1008bPM.s.8">Functional Design fromö Christine initial functional design was made and to
be develop further as per sales and user interface suggestions
User Interface from :</sent> <sent nite:id="IS1008bPM.s.9">First draft of user interface is ready and acceptable
to all and need to submit to the management for approval.</sent>
<sent nite:id="IS1008bPM.s.10">Sales and Marketing Plan: ED Price structure and product features were
discussed with various new features like Speech Recognization and other
features.</sent>  
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 

</participant_decisions>
<participant_problems nite:id="IS1008bPM.pproblems.1">
 <sent nite:id="IS1008bPM.s.11">Coming Budget to be discussed with the meeting
And time frame and risk analysis to be made</sent>
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 

</participant_problems>
</nite:root>
